COF connect as a.
Mhm.
As a proof of concept, right,
and I think it would be also instrumental
for this team members to to help out on
on that POC as well.
Sure.
Yeah, so I think, you know, Sean,
I think you hit the big ones that,
you know, are on the plate,
especially the kids Foot Locker,
Foot Locker conversion stuff that's
probably taken up a lot of the team's
time right now. A lot of pieces to that,
a lot of stuff there. And then
Yeah,
whatever comes out of this whole
store-to-store process,
it's being pushed straight. But yeah,
those are some of the bigger ones. Yeah,
yeah, as of today, yes.
Those are the priorities as of today.
So at 1207 P.m. So
Yeah.
So, I'm not, you know, if that's...
You know that I think that's helpful for
you guys from a from a Capgemini
perspective.
Anything anything that you heard there
that.
that makes you nervous or is, you know.
But I think they will go ahead, Debasish.
Yeah, hi, Deba here. My name is Debasish.
You guys can call me Deba as well. Yeah,
so I just wanted to know on the target
platform, like what is it going to be?
And if you can throw more details on the
Zero Connect.
POC work that we're going to do that
would be really helpful.
Yep, that is currently in somewhere else,
someone's mind, like mine. We're drafted,
we're drafted initiative.
We start early engagements.
Yeah.
I'll try to see if there was a recording
of the early discussions.
I can definitely send that over to you if
I didn't lose the recording for those.
But yeah,
I think there is a lot of issues that we
need at arms and we need to actually take
it out of our heads and get going.
So I'll see whatever I already have
drafted out, Debasish,
and I'll forward that to you.
Yeah, that would be great, Lucas.
There has been a lot of discovery that
was done as well on MPF side by the
And.
merchandise pricing system.
It was actually some of those were with
the help of Goten.
I don't know if you guys know,
and I don't know if you guys know the
Korean team that is supporting Mainframe
today, Ananda, Goten, and Amapa.
Yeah, I got them, so yeah,
I mean actually they are part of our team
only, the support part of it, so yeah,
we are, we we know them very well.
Yeah, I know, I know you do, uh, for Deba,
we'll, I'll share up.
Yeah.
No, they, I will introduce them. Actually,
they are new to the engagement at the
Yeah.
found, right? So,
I think there's they have had a couple of
Is it?
calls with Anindita just to kind of get a
background of Footlocker, but yeah,
we will make sure that that that the
knowledge gets passed on whatever they
know at least.
Yeah, that's good.
Yeah, but I'll forward to,
I'll forward whatever was done in the
past for MDO,
some early on discover it also,
so you have visibility.
You guys got your access in Jira already?
I have access to Teams,
but I cannot access Jira yet.
And.
Yeah.
Looks like my first call is working on it,
but I don't have access yet.
Yeah, I put the request in.
I'm not sure that they've granted them
Yeah.
yet. They're working on it.
Yeah.
We'll figure out, and whenever you do,
I'll forward you the Jira IDs and it
should be able to see it.
Is there a weekly or a daily stand-up or
cadence that these guys can start
participating for lupus and call?
Yeah,
we do have one on the Mainframe team that
Anatha and Gotham are involved in.
So yeah,
we can get these guys invited to that one
as well. Yep,
I'll have Agnes send out an invite.
Yeah.
Yeah. Hey, Carl,
I was thinking about just the dynamics
for Dan.
I'm assuming you would agree with that,
but they will be primarily under your
team. And whenever I think, Mondhe,
we will actually have need from Dan,
we can bring them over ad hoc to the
To the MOPS team, to the pricing team,
we're...
Yeah, we'll definitely share. Yeah, yeah,
figure out how to share them. Yep, yep,
no problem there.
But you, but you, you're good with, like,
you're gonna utilize and and whatever
current load in your team as a primary,
right? And then when it comes some demand,
we're gonna give you, like,
and then again,
Sandeep can plan with Agnes as well.
We'll try to plan in Q4 ready some high
level goals that we want and right to
have.
some sort of capacity already planned out,
right?
Then we can organize the ceremonies as
well.
So then we need to be fully allocated on
both.
I think it would be a waste of time on
those ceremonies, right?
But I was envisioning then to be fully on
your team,
Yeah.
and then whenever there is a need for
them to be participating in the
ceremonies,
we can expand and deep dive on ours.
If you need to join yours as well, too,
we'll go it away.
Yeah, I agree. Yeah,
there's no such pulling them in, right?
Yeah.
So it's like, whatever they're working on,
yeah, we'll get them, yep.
That makes sense.
Okay.
Um, Debasish or Sidharth,
any other questions from your side?
No, I don't have any questions as of now.
Ohh yeah.
Yeah, I I just have one.
So, Khan,
you mentioned a few minutes back,
Okay.
the team is more busy in the conversions,
right?
What are these conversions exactly about?
Like,
is it one legacy platform to another,
or how is it?
A little bit elaborate information on the
conversion would be helpful.
Yeah, it's basically, what I'll say,
consolidating 2 banners within our system.
That's probably the best way to look at
it. We look at things as a division.
So we have a division of stores,
probably 2,
300 stores that are called Kids Foot
Locker, and they're under their own.
identification, basically,
their store numbers, their items,
things like that.
And we are basically merging them into
our main Footlocker branch, which is,
you know, 800 plus stores.
So we are converting those stores over.
And so.
A lot of the history files and a lot of
their identifications are changing.
The conversion is supposed to be sometime
in April next year,
so there's just a lot of work that needs
to be done leading up to that.
I set the diagram here,
a card that somebody put together on a
high level, what that is.
There's a lot of information there.
Yes, there is.
You ask and you shall receive.
There is a lot of megas there.
This.
Thanks for sharing that, yeah.
Okay, yeah, go to.
But we'll get more into the details. Yeah,
it's not like it's changing systems or
Absolutely.
anything like that.
It's just converting data within our
systems.
Yeah.
Yeah, thank you.
Okay, so as next step,
I think while we are waiting for the VDI
and the Jira,
they will start attending those meeting
cadences and Carl, I mean,
obviously these guys have access to Teams,
right? And so, I mean,
you can reach out to them also at any
point in time if there are any immediate
tasks on.
deliverables that needs to be handled
over to. And then Lucas,
you're going to share the SOPs or the
artifacts that we can have them get speed
up to.
And I will also make sure that I patch
them up with Anindita and Gautam for them
to get some background of the cloud.
Perfect, yeah.
Yeah, I mean,
I think if they can work with the
existing, you know, L1,
L2 team on high level knowledge transfer,
Exactly. Yep.
that'd be awesome. And then, and then,
you know, where,
Shah.
where they start to kind of fall off on
the detailed knowledge perspective,
then reach out to Carl and
And he'll get, you know,
one of the three folks to to kind of do
walkthroughs at a, you know,
at a detail level, so that...
You know,
so that we can kind of manage the the KT,
Yep.
Yeah.
um, and not and not completely hit,
you know, uh, Carl's team.
Yeah, you know,
exclusively for the ZOS Connect,
I will give you the recordings of the
early conversations and there will be a
kickoff and some planning that we're
going to do potentially for next month.
I will keep you in the loop for that.
Yeah, thanks, Lucas.
Okay, so and yeah,
I think should we put over a touch base
early next week or later this week just
to kind of take a stock of the situation
or we are going to cover that in the
daily stand-ups as to how these things
are progressing.
We don't all attend the daily stand-up,
so if you want a group with all of us,
Oh, okay, yeah, great.
then you should put something on the
board.
If it's just kind of within the working
team,
Shutter.
then you'll be able to handle that in the
stand-up.
Sure thing, that that that works well.
I'll put something just later this week,
I'll put something on the calendar for
everyone just to take a stop of the
situation if there are any blockers and
things like that.
Thank you so much.
I think that's what we had.
Any other follows from anyone, please?
Or did you put already their cloud PC
requests in?
So the video process changes lately,
so I know it's a cloud PC now.
I put in a VDI request.
Is that the same thing? So I put in VDI,
Oh.
Jira, Confluence.
I think they got their AD and e-mail.
Setup.
So let me,
there is a specific form for Cloud PCs.
Now the VDI is cut over.
Some people are still calling VDI,
but it got cut over maybe six months ago.
You can send me the request, one of them,
I can triple check.
I was going to ask to make sure that they
request Developer and not standard.
Because the standard ones, ohh,
you selected.
I did, I did. Yeah, no, I did.
I did request Developer for both of them.
Yep.
Yeah, standard is slow, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's stuck.
Alright, yeah, so...
So I think we're okay there.
I can give you the request numbers, Lucas,
if you want to check them out.
Yep, OK, is it? Yep.
So.
Man, I wanna on the sides,
did did you request all the VDI Jira
Confluence for the QI or QE? Okay, okay.
Do you all right,
No, not yet.
That's in the process right now, yeah.
This is.
do you need help with that or you got it
covered?
So I think I got it covered.
I'll reach out to you if, yeah.
OK, alright, no worries.
Just gonna make sure we go to the right
one, so it's a little bit hit or miss, so,
Yeah, yeah, so this morning,
Carl and I were talking about.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
we were going back and forth on that, so,
so...
I got the ADs completed for all the QE,
so that's taken care of with that.
OK.
Yeah.
Perfect. Thank you. Alright.
I guess we are good then, huh?
Awesome.
Alright, thanks guys.
All right, thanks all.
Yep. Thank you. Thank you.
Sorry.
Thank you.